

Arda Burak Atila

Software Developer & Data Analyst

☑ ardatila13@gmail.com **೨** +90(533)3115503 **♀** Maltepe, 34854 istanbul

Profile

I graduated in computer science from University of Pécs. Focused on web development since 2018. My first programming skill that Python, React, and also improved my java skill. I have some projects which are related to ParNote works and I have a Vaadin spring boot project on my GitHub.I am aiming to improve myself based on lifelong learning and increasing human beings' prosperity by developing software to make living easier. I always looking for learning new skills, have extra responsibilities, and grow professionally. I can work in busy, pressurized environments where high standards are expected.

Education

Computer Science BSc

Sep 2019 - Sep 2022

University of Pécs, Hungary

- Final GPA: 3.50 / 5.00
- Final School Project: Prepared a thesis on Internet of Things security.

Preparatory School

Sep 2018 - Jun 2019

International Studies Center, Hungary

High School

Sep 2014 - Jun 2017

Private Atasehir Okyanus Science High School, Turkey

Experience

Junior DWH & BI Consultant

Oct 2022 - Jan 2023

Smartmind, Turkey

Worked at Memorial Hospital DWH Project

- Created attribute mapping from an Excel sheet.
- Created data with 3 schemas in the ODS layer, the connection and data types of its data have been changed and converted from MySQL (Source) to postqre SQL (Target Database).
- Tables were combined by performing table analysis.
- The tables for the schemas were created on postgre SQL.
- Data transfers ETL started via Microsoft SSIS.
- Created temporary tables for the ODS layer via SSIS tool
- Used ETL from ODS to Data Warehouse (DWH).
- Consulted the Memorial data management team.

Software Development Intern

Jul 2021 - Aug 2021

Trio Mobil, Turkey

• Used Postman for API testing.

Personal details

Date of birth November 13, 1998

Driver's license **B2**

Website archely.github.

io/PortfolioWebsite

LinkedIn

linkedin.com/in/arda-burakatila-a5a126141

GitHub

github.com/archely

Skills

PL/SQL

DWH Architect

MSSQL,PostqreSQL, Oracle

ETL SSIS

NoSQL MongoDB

Python Pandas Library

React

HTML,CSS,Bootsrap

Postman

GitHub

- Learned GET, POST, PULL, and DELETE methods.
- Learned how to send requests to API.
- Performed API testing with the Axios method over Javascript and react.

Software Development Intern (Remote)

Jul 2021 - Aug 2021

Crede Consulting & Data Services, Turkey

- Delivered a small software collecting data from a free test using Java and RegularExpressions.
- Used Regular Expression method, analyzes all data to find the keyword. Data:(https://www.ilan.gov.tr/)
- Used postman test API for all checkin databases.

Project

ParNote

- ParNote works for my final university project. I completed with my friends. The project structure is twopart. One part is the backend side repo: "ParNoteApp/ParNote" and another part is the UI side repo: "ParNoteApp/ParNoteUI".
- Project languages used Kotlin, svelte, SCSS, JavaScript, and Bootstrap. We used the kanban method for stages.
- My task is to get information such as passwords, Recaptcha, and log in from the database with API (Kotlin Language) and I created token and email verification for security. In the UI part, I developed and designed the about me section of the login page using bootstrap and svelte.
- A note application which allows you to add, edit and share personal notes, collaborate with your friends and moreover discover other people notes.

Certificates

Linux Administration: The Complete Linux Bootcamp for 2023

The Complete Oracle SQL Bootcamp (2023)

SSIS Eğitim Videosu Serisi

Komple Uygulamalı Web Geliştirme Eğitimi

Amazon Job Roles in the Cloud, AWS

Introduction to Git and Github, Coursera

Python, Coursera

Uygulamalarla SQL Öğreniyorum, Udemy

REST API
API Testing
Linux
Microsoft Office
TeamWork
Postman
Languages

English